export const reactQuestions = [
  {
    correctAnswer: "Dijkstra's algorithm",
    options: [
      "Prim's algorithm",
      "Kruskal's algorithm",
      "Dijkstra's algorithm",
      "Floyd-Warshall algorithm",
    ],
    question: "Which algorithm is used to find the shortest path in a graph?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Dynamic Programming",
    options: [
      "Divide and Conquer",
      "Greedy",
      "Dynamic Programming",
      "Backtracking",
    ],
    question:
      "Which programming paradigm involves breaking down a problem into smaller subproblems and solving them recursively?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Static Binding",
    options: [
      "Dynamic Binding",
      "Static Binding",
      "Early Binding",
      "Late Binding",
    ],
    question:
      "What type of binding determines the type of a variable at compile time?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Polymorphism",
    options: ["Encapsulation", "Inheritance", "Polymorphism", "Abstraction"],
    question:
      "Which of the following OOP concepts allows objects to take on different forms?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Multithreading",
    options: [
      "Multiprocessing",
      "Multithreading",
      "Concurrency",
      "Parallelism",
    ],
    question:
      "Which technique allows a program to execute multiple tasks simultaneously?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Database Schema",
    options: [
      "Database Table",
      "Database Instance",
      "Database Schema",
      "Database Query",
    ],
    question: "What defines the structure of a database and its relationships?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Cloud Computing",
    options: ["Virtualization", "Cloud Computing", "Big Data", "DevOps"],
    question:
      "Which model provides computing resources over the internet on a pay-as-you-go basis?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Agile Development",
    options: ["Waterfall Development", "Agile Development", "Scrum", "Kanban"],
    question:
      "Which software development methodology emphasizes iterative development and continuous feedback?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "UnitOfWork",
    options: ["Repository", "UnitOfWork", "Context", "Entity Framework"],
    question:
      "In the context of ORM (Object-Relational Mapping), which component manages changes to multiple objects as a single transaction?",
  },
  {
    correctAnswer: "Continuous Integration",
    options: [
      "Continuous Deployment",
      "Continuous Integration",
      "Continuous Delivery",
      "DevOps",
    ],
    question:
      "Which practice involves automating the build, testing, and merging of code changes on a regular basis?",
  },
];
